原创翻译  双语字幕
我叫卡拉·佐·艾尔
My name is Kara Zor-El.
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我来自氪星
I'm from Krypton.
我来到这颗星球避难
I'm a refugee on this planet.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我被派往地球保护我的堂弟
I was sent to Earth to protect my cousin.
但我的太空舱被击中后偏离路线
But my pod got knocked off course.
在我到达地球之时
And by the time I got here,
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我的堂弟已经长大  成为了超人
my cousin had already grown up and become... Superman.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我隐藏了我的真实身份
I hid who I really was
直到最近的一起事故
until one day when an accident
迫使我向世界揭示了自己的身份
forced me to reveal myself to the world.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
对于大多数人  我只是凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
To most people, I'm a reporter at CatCo Worldwide Media.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
但私下里  我与收养家庭的姐姐一同为超查部工作
But in secret I work with my adopted sister at the DEO
保护这颗我称之为家园的星球
to protect this planet I call my home
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不受任何人的伤害
from anyone that means to cause it harm.
我是超女
I am Supergirl.
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
谢谢你一直在我身边
Thank you for standing by my side
让我自己处理这件事
and letting me handle this by myself.
那你另一个案子呢
And your other investigation?
守护者算什么
Guardian who?
我爱你  曼彻斯特
I love you, Manchester.
菲奥娜
Fiona.
菲奥娜之前在调查他  我想接着追查
Fiona was looking into him. And I tried to follow up.
佩特赛利警官
Officer Petrocelli?
这是哈伦·艾尔
This is the Harun-El.
对于它  我们还有太多不了解的地方
There's so many things we don't know about it.
它的用途  力量  危险
Its uses, its powers, its dangers.
我们准备进入试验的第二阶段
We're ready to begin phase two of our trials.
我觉得感恩节没别的  就是要吃南瓜派
I'm sorry, but Thanksgiving for me is all about pumpkin.
-什么  -真的
- What? - Yes.
苹果派好吃多了  也更具美国特色
Apple is way better and more American.
可肉豆蔻  姜
But the nutmeg, the ginger,
还有那一小团鲜奶油
and the dollop of fresh whipped cream.
好吧  我喜欢听你说"一小团"
Okay, I love it when you say "Dollop."
来  我们走
Come on, let's go.
这里过去是个美好的社区
This used to be a nice neighborhood.
但你们却滋生了
Until you infested it.
美好算是过誉了
Nice is overrated.
我们走  我们走
Let's go. Let's go.
去咬那些垃圾
Go get those scum!
佩特赛利
Petrocelli.
朋友  还记得我吗
Hey, friend-o. Remember me?
真奇怪  狗狗通常很喜欢我
That's weird. Dogs usually love me.
我要闪人了  伙计
I'm outta here, man.
再靠近一步我就弄断他的脖子
Take a step and I break his neck.
谢了  但情况在我控制之下
Thanks, but I had it under control.
曼彻斯特  对吗
Manchester, right?
我们见过面
We-we've met.
是啊  我记得
Yeah, I remember.
你在这做什么
So, what are you doing here?
散散步而已
You know, just out for a walk
我看到这些人在骚扰一对有爱的外星情侣
and I saw this lot harassing a nice alien couple.
美国最后的暮光
"致所有真正的自由之子
"To all true Children of Liberty
我们相信这个国家属于我们
who believe this country is ours.
我们必须抵制外星人灾害"
We must resist the alien scourge."
这是一份宣言
This is a manifesto.
这个自由代表是谁
Who is this Agent Liberty?
我们都是
We all are.
超 女
第四季 第六集
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我的车被淋湿了  这些传单全糊在了上面
My car was wet and these leaflets stuck to it like paper mache.
没关系  我正要开始检查
It's okay. I was just about to check the efficiency
哈伦·艾尔治疗肿瘤的效率
of the Harun-El treatment on the tumors.
他们自称为自由之子
They call themselves the Children of Liberty.
我想就是这些人
I think these are the ones
一直称呼守护者为人类英雄
who kept calling Guardian a human hero.
真瘆人
So creepy.
我希望詹姆斯今天能公开谴责他们
I'm hoping James will denounce them today.
我帮他定了上肖恩·秋的电视节目
I booked him on Sean Chiu's television program,
-《今日辩论》  -真的吗
- The Counterpoint Daily. - You did?
我超爱那节目
I love that show.
好吧  我们得稳定心率
Okay, we gotta get the rhythm back.
心率194  还在上升
BPM is 194 and rising.
充能
Charge.
肿瘤还在增大
The tumors were still growing.
做活组织检查  销毁样本
Take a biopsy, we'll destroy the sample.
我们还有两个治疗方案
We still have two protocols left.
你这是打算治愈癌症  肯定要花时间
You're trying to cure cancer, it's gonna take time.
自由之子向世界宣布了自己的存在
The Children of Liberty announcing themselves to the world.
多克斯特工已经开始调查自由代表的身份
Agent Dox is already working on identifying Agent Liberty,
并试图找出宣言中是否有隐藏信息
and trying to find if there's a deeper message in the manifesto.
为什么  这些是人类仇恨组织小打小闹
Why? I mean, these are the rantings of a human hate group.
联邦调查局会处理的
The FBI will deal with it.
但这可能很危险
But this could be dangerous.
这是有先例的
There's precedent.
从德国的白玫瑰组织
From the White Rose in Germany
到1954年危地马拉的中情局
to the CIA in Guatemala in 1954.
这样的传单过去常用来引发起义活动
Leaflets like this, they were used to activate uprisings.
这不是我们的管辖范围  局长
It's not our purview, Director.
说到管辖范围
And speaking of purview,
你发现这些传单时在哪
where were you when you found this?
我正在阻止面具人袭击两名外星人
I was stopping an attack on two aliens by men in masks.
是在哪呢
But where?
市中心公园
Midtown Park.
你接到去那巡逻的命令了吗
Were you ordered to patrol there?
我去是因为我听到
I went because I heard--
你接到去那巡逻的命令了吗
Were you ordered to patrol there?
没有  女士
No, ma'am.
我知道你过去行动完全自由
I know you've had free rein in the past,
但现在情况不同了
but things are different now.
假如你想阻止抢劫  加入纳市警局
If you want to intervene in muggings, join the NCPD.
这里是超查部
This is the DEO.
我们应对的是更危急的情况
We swim in deeper waters.
我们的资源不会用来调查这份宣言
Our resources will not be used to investigate this manifesto.
你叫多克斯特工做其他任务上去
You tell Agent Dox to return to his other assignments,
明白了吗
is that clear?
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
我或许不是钢铁女侠  但你们要是逼我
I may not be the Woman of Steel, but if you push me
就会发现我也不屈不折
you will find I do not bend.
解散
Dismissed.
还有一件事
And one more thing.
我今天带了些红薯派来  就在自助餐厅
I brought some sweet potato pie today. It's in the cafeteria.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
她完全固执己见
She's completely dug her heels in here.
权力都在她手里
She has all of the power.
那我们只能听她的吗
So we're just gonna listen to her?
什么  才不要
What? No way.
-不  我们还是要调查这件事  -是啊
- No, we're still investigating this. - Yeah.
她要是再像《哈利波特》的乌姆里奇一样
And if she gets any more Dolores Umbridge-y,
我就学韦斯莱双胞胎
I'm going full Weasley twin.
没错  再说谁会吃她的派
Yeah, and who would eat that pie?
-肯定有毒  -毫无疑问
- It's for sure poisoned. - Absolutely.
我定位了撒传单的无人机
I've located the drones that dropped the manifesto.
可惜无法追踪它们
Unfortunately, they're untraceable.
没有印记  没有序列号
No prints, no serial numbers.
布莱尼  很遗憾地告诉你
Brainy, I'm sorry to say that
哈雷上校已正式命令你
Colonel Haley has officially ordered you
-停止调查  -好
- to stop the investigation. - Okay.
什么  不不不
What? No, no, no.
你明白我的意思  对吧
You understand what I'm saying, right?
我向你保证我们沟通上的困难已成为过去
I assure you our communication difficulties are in the past.
我的调查就此终止
Consider my investigation terminated.
不  布莱尼
No, no, Brainy,
我们想让你继续调查这件事
we want you to keep looking into it.
好吧  我糊涂了
Okay, I'm confused.
所以我才使了眼色
It's-it's why I winked.
是的
Ah, yes.
我会完全保密地继续进行调查
I shall continue my investigation in complete secrecy.
给你的
For you.
我不
I don't...
我发誓他最后肯定会害我被解雇
I swear that he's going to get me fired by the end of the day.
对了  伊莉莎来短信了
Oh, by the way, Eliza texted.
明天的感恩节晚宴你负责蔓越莓酱
You're on cranberry sauce for Thanksgiving dinner tomorrow.
我哪有时间去杂货店买
When am I supposed to go to the grocery store?
自由之子那天晚上
Why were the Children of Liberty
为什么上街巡逻
out there patrolling in the first place?
佩特赛利会搞砸整个计划
Petrocelli could blow this whole thing.
确保他们都保持低调
Just make sure they all lay low
直到那一刻来临
until the time comes.
抱歉用了这么久
Sorry it took so long.
外面简直乱套了  但我东西都买齐了
It was a zoo but I got everything.
我买了红薯  面包卷  我
I got the sweet potatoes, I got the rolls, and I...
我想我买了甜胡椒粉
...think I got the allspice.
我的英雄
My hero.
我有些好消息
Well, I have some good news.
看起来我们这个月
It looks like we're gonna be able to
又有钱还按揭了
make our mortgage payment again this month.
当你许下"无论富贵或贫困"的誓言
Oh, well, when you sign up for "Richer or for poorer"
你肯定希望不仅仅只是贫困
you kinda hope it's not always for poorer.
是"不管贫困"
Is it "For poorer"?
还是只是"贫穷"
Isn't it just "For poor"?
我不记得了  我当时没上心
You know, I don't remember. I wasn't actually paying attention.
妈妈  爸爸  快来看这个
Mom, Dad, you gotta see this!
看啊
Look.
许多人被自由之子的宣言震惊了
Most were surprised by this Children of Liberty manifesto.
但是  前历史教授  本·洛克伍德
However, former history professor, Ben Lockwood,
早就对此事有所察觉  请看
had a little more foresight. Take a look.
你知道这事吗
Did you know about this?
整个历史中  被压迫者
Throughout history, the downtrodden
总能在被主流遗忘之前
have found ways to make their voices heard
找到方法让他们的声音被听到
before the mainstream forgets about them.
但讽刺的是
But the irony in this case
目前的主流  人类
is that the mainstream, humanity,
才是被压迫的一方
are the downtrodden.
爸爸  你出名了
Dad, you're famous.
那是本·洛克伍德在评论
That was Professor Ben Lockwood commenting
当下人类与外星人的关系现状
on the current state of human-alien relations...
我会去的  谢谢你
I'll be there. Thank you.
打扰到你了吗  奥尔森先生
Am I interrupting, Mr. Olsen?
欢迎随时来找我
Always got time for you.
包里是什么
Uh, what's in the bag?
你为什么不看看
Why don't you take a look?
谢谢
Thank you.
你真宠坏我了
You spoil me.
是啊
Yeah.
真棒
Oh, yeah.
你今天没准就有能穿出去的机会了
And, you know, you might have the opportunity to wear it,
也许就在几小时之后
maybe in the next couple of hours.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我给你定了上今天的《今日辩论》
I booked you to go on Counterpoint Daily today.
我觉得你应该上电视批判自由之子
I think you should go on TV and disavow the Children of Liberty.
我知道你已经远离那类人了
I know you moved away from that idea,
但是事情升级了  好吗
but things have escalated, okay?
他们的宣言充满了仇恨言论
Their manifesto was filled with hate speech.
我只是希望你能先和我商量下
Yeah, I just wish that you would have checked with me first.
今天我不行
I can't do that today.
为什么
Well, why not?
在市长那事之后  我联络了本·洛克伍德
Well, after the Mayor's event, I reached out to Ben Lockwood.
花了些时间
And it took some time,
但我联络上了真正的自由之子
but I got connected with some actual Children of Liberty.
我今天会去和他们见面
I'm meeting with them today.
你要与国内恐怖组织会面吗
You're meeting with a domestic terror group?
去了解他们是谁
To learn who they are.
最终  去采访自由代表本人
And eventually, get an interview with Agent Liberty himself.
你自己也说了  那些人敬仰我
You said it yourself, these people admire me,
也许我可以利用这一点改变他们的想法
and maybe I can use that to change minds.
这是我在他们发表仇恨言论之前说的
I said that before they dropped their hateful agenda on the world.
那就更加要去了  不是吗
All the more reason to go now, isn't it?
这更加说明他们可能会动用到暴力
It's all the more reason to think they might resort to violence,
尤其是他们的人类代言人加入的话
especially if they've got their human posterboy in their midst.
人类代言人
Human posterboy?
你觉得我办不到  是不是
You don't think I can do this, do you?
-你要和谁见面  -我不知道
- Who are you meeting with? - I don't know.
你要在哪里和他们见面
Where are you meeting them?
他们会在见面前15分钟打给我
They're gonna call me 15 minutes beforehand.
所以是在一个未知地点见不明身份的人
So it's an undisclosed location with unknown context.
这就是记者死掉的情节  詹姆斯
This is how journalists end up dead, James.
我不是大部分记者
Most journalists are not me.
所以我怎么想都无所谓
So it doesn't matter what I think.
这事不行  这是工作
Not about this. This is work.
"这是工作"
"This is work."
那你的老板给你定了
Well, then your boss has booked
在大型电视台上亮相的工作
a major television appearance for you.
自己去处理吧
So figure it out.
我最喜欢的火星人
My favorite Martian.
抱歉  估计经常有人对你这么说
Sorry, you probably get that all the time.
你没回复我的邀请
You didn't reply to my invitation.
哦对  朝圣日
Right. Uh, yeah, Pilgrim Day.
我就是不太感兴趣
I'm just not up for it, man.
好吧  我就是担心
Right. It's just that I was worried that
那些传单可能会激发你不好的感觉
those leaflets might stir up some bad feelings for you.
-没什么我处理不了的  -那好
- Nothing I can't handle. - Right.
也许来顿火鸡晚餐能有帮助
Well, maybe a turkey dinner will help.
是个小聚会  我们很希望你能加入
It's a small gathering, we'd love to have you.
但我不能保证没有字谜游戏
Although I can't promise there won't be Charades.
虽然我这么爱字谜...
As much as I love Charades...
我明白  我明白
I understand, I understand.
那好吧  如果你改变了想法
Well, look, man, if you change your mind
这是我朋友的地址
here's my friend's address.
荣恩
J'onn.
谢谢你能想着我
Thanks for thinking of me.
没什么
Sure.
好吧
Right.
我们聊到哪了
Where were we?
对了  你刚要开口招供来着
Oh, yeah, you were about to start talking.
詹姆斯  我这里有关于昨晚袭击的800字证言
Oh, James, I have 800 words on the assault last night
是戴着自由代表面具的人说的
by the men wearing Agent Liberty masks.
好
Yeah.
-一切都还好吗  -还好
- Everything okay? - Yeah.
莉娜给我定了上一个会谈节目
Uh, Lena booked me on this round table thing.
那太好了
That's great!
不  不好吗
Isn't... Isn't that great?
她应该先和我说一声的
Um, she should've told me first. You know?
好吧  我本来准备
Okay, so I made plans to
去见自由之子的人
meet with somebody from Children of Liberty,
但现在她想让我上电视批判他们
and now she wants me to go on a TV show and denounce them.
她是在担心你作为守护者的形象
Well, she's worried about your image as Guardian.
我知道莉娜有时候比较强硬
I know Lena can be forceful,
但是她会保护所爱之人
but she protects the ones she loves.
她不总是对的
She's not always right.
但大部分时候是对的
She's right most of the time.
你是站哪边的
Whose side are you on?
为你好你的两边我都站
I'm on both of your sides.
但我还是不会去那个会谈节目
But I'm still not doing the round table.
-我可以去  -不不不
- I can do it. - No. No, no, no.
还有几小时就开始了
It's only in a few hours and
去之前还要做很多准备工作
there's lot of preparation that needs to be done.
而新闻室里因为放假一半人都不在
And half the newsroom is gone because of the holiday.
我是说  算了吧
I mean... No.
没事  我让尼娅帮我就好
That's fine. I'll just ask Nia to help me. Where's...
你是说尼娅·纳尔
You, you mean Nia Nal,
现在上班睡觉的那位吗
the one who's literally asleep on the job?
不是  她可没
No, she's not...
巧克力咖啡豆子
Chocolate-covered espresso beans.
尼娅
Nia.
你感觉还好吗
You feeling all right?
不好  求你别开除我
Oh. Oh, no. Please don't fire me.
不不不
No, no, no, no.
没人会开除你
No one's gonna fire you.
你活干的很好
You do amazing work
当你  醒着的时候
when you're...awake.
抱歉我之前没提到过
I'm sorry I didn't say anything before,
但我有爱睡觉的病
but I have that sleep thing.
就是那个随时随地会睡着的病
The one that causes you to fall asleep at random times.
-嗜睡症  -没错
- Narcolepsy? - Yes!
就是那个  嗜睡症
That's it, narcolepsy.
尼娅  这可是个很严重的病啊
Oh. Well, Nia, that's a serious illness.
你看医生了吗
Have you seen a doctor?
有  以前在华盛顿特区看过
Yeah, yeah, back in DC.
我在这里还没找到合适的医生
I haven't found anyone here yet.
如果有什么我们能帮忙的...
Well, if there's anything we can do...
尽管开口就行
Yeah, don't hesitate to ask for help.
没错
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
我去把自由之子的信息拿给你
Uh, let me get you that information on Children of Liberty.
有什么发现吗
Hey, have you found anything?
完全没查到自由代表的身份
Nothing on the identity of Agent Liberty.
但是我在传单上找到了10011种代码
However, I was able to find 10,011 codes within the leaflet.
上面全是代码
It is literally littered with codes.
比如  如果你弄乱每第七个字母
For example, if you scramble every seventh letter,
明确地指出拉奥语中一个常见的词
it clearly indicates a common phrase in the Raolian language.
火腿三明治
"Ham sandwich."
一个以火鸡来庆祝的节日
On a holiday celebrated exclusively with turkey,
那简直就是当面打脸
that is just a slap in the face.
这是最有意义的代码吗
And that is the most promising code?
特工们
Agents,
请汇报一下你们目前的工作
a briefing on your current work, please.
完蛋了
Oh, no.
你逮到我了  上校
Uh, you caught me, Colonel.
我必须坦白
I must confess,
你的红薯派实在太好吃了
your sweet potato pie is so delicious
激起了我去找食谱的念头
that it inspired me to search for a recipe
想自己做来吃
and make one of my very own.
在感恩节那天做
For Thanksgiving.
很抱歉我因为你那美味的烘培而分心了
I apologize for allowing your masterful baking to distract me
没做好重要的超查部工作
from important DEO business.
继续工作  多克斯特工
Back to work, Agent Dox.
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers.
是的  长官
Yes, ma'am.
艾丽克斯  有些人类的举止
You see, Alex, some human behaviors
需要从实践中学习
require experiential learning.
我已掌握的人际技能增加了"临场掩护"
Now I can add "Covering on the spot" to my skills of mastery.
她差点就发现你了
Yes, well, that was a little too close.
继续保持低调
So just keep a low profile
有发现就通知我
and let me know if you find anything.
掩护得好
Good, good job.
没错
Yes.
-我会保持低调  -请对你自己说
- I'll keep a low profile. - To yourself, please.
是詹姆斯·奥尔森吗
James Olsen?
如假包换
In the flesh.
你真人各自更高大
You're a lot bigger in person.
告诉我  你是做什么的
Tell me, what do you bench?
一般情况下  贩毒
Normally, drug dealers.
你也很幽默
You're funny, too.
我是说对不起
Oh, man. I mean... I'm sorry,
真的很荣幸见到你
it's just such an honor to meet you.
你身为守护者真的激发了我们很多人
Your work as Guardian has inspired so many of us
站出来为正义而战
to stand up and fight for justice.
谢谢你
Thanks, man.
-你叫什么  -对了
- What's your name? - Oh, yeah...
抱歉  我只是有点紧张  我叫汤姆
Sorry, I'm just a little nervous. Tom.
汤姆  很高兴认识你
Tom, nice to meet you, brother.
我也是
Me too.
你准备好了吗
You, uh, you ready to go?
-我们走吧  -好
- Let's do it. - Okay.
你要把包扔在后座吗
Do you wanna throw that in the back?
-好  -好
- Yeah, sure. - Cool.
你不怕狗吧
You're not afraid of dogs, are you?
心脏还在衰竭
The hearts keep dying.
我们电击了三次  但心脏毫无起色
We shocked it three times but it wouldn't revive.
你量过肿瘤的大小了吗
Did you measure the tumor?
3.6毫米
3.6 millimeters.
肿瘤在变大
The tumors are growing.
氦辐射应该能完全将肿瘤收缩的
The He radiation should be shrinking them completely.
我们何不留下来  调整一下协议呢
Why don't we stay and adjust the protocol?
不  你回家陪陪家人吧
No. No, you go home to your family.
反正我也没那么喜欢他们
I don't really like them that much anyway.
不  我们可以找到办法的
No, we can figure this out.
不  今天我们留在这里
No. We're not gonna come up with any solutions
也想不出办法的
staying here today.
把心脏烧掉吧
Incinerate it.
心脏没有烧掉  为什么烧不掉
The heart didn't burn up. Why didn't it burn up?
不可能  再试一次
That's impossible. Try again.
-是哈伦·艾尔造成的吗  -肯定是
- Did the Harun-El do this? - It must have.
哈伦让心脏坚不可摧
It made the heart invincible.
作为凯特科的记者
As a reporter for CatCo,
你认为媒体在日渐高涨的反外星人情绪中
what role do you think the media should be playing
应该扮演什么样的角色呢
in the rising anti-alien sentiment?
媒体的目标是保证公众听到每个人的心声
The goal of the media is to ensure that every voice is heard.
无知会产生恐惧
Ignorance breeds fear.
所以我们撰写越多真实有力的新闻
So the more factual, dynamic news stories we write,
包括外星人的新闻  我们就越少...
including about aliens, the less we will...
-尼娅  -我在听你说
- Nia! - I'm listening.
尼娅  我们必须带你去看医生
Nia, we have got to get you help.
你应该来我家和我们一起过感恩节
Hey, you know, you should come to my place on Thanksgiving.
我妈会来
My mom will be there,
她认识市里所有顶尖的医生
and she knows all the top doctors in the city.
她可以帮你
She can help you.
不了  我不用...
No, I don't--
我们准备好了  丹弗斯小姐
We're ready for you, Miss Danvers.
好的
Uh, got it. Yup.
谢谢你
Thank you.
等一下  等一下
Okay, wait, wait.
我很善于给人打气
I'm good at this.
你会好好表现的
You're gonna do great.
你有满腔激情  头脑聪慧
You are passionate, you're intelligent.
头发还那么好看  你挑染了吗
Your hair looks amazing. Did you get highlights?
-嗯  -去征服他们吧
- Yeah. - Go get 'em.
好像我才是你的导师吧
I thought I was the mentor.
卡拉·丹弗斯  谢谢你来参加我们的节目
Kara Danvers, thank you so much for joining us on the show.
谢谢你们邀请我
Thanks for having me.
这是你的辩论对手
And this is your counterpoint.
我叫本·洛克伍德
Ben Lockwood.
很高兴认识你
It's very nice to meet you.
没什么事吧
Everything okay?
嗯  只是我太太
Yeah, it's just my wife.
临节购物清单还在增加
Last minute grocery list keeps on growing.
我什么时候能见到自由代表
So when do I get to meet Agent Liberty?
在你面前的就是
You're talking to him.
你就是自由代表吗
You're Agent Liberty?
我们全都是自由代表
Well, we're all Agents of Liberty.
不  我是说发号施令的那个人
Nah. I mean the big guy.
在传单上签名的那个人  我希望能采访他
Guy who signed the leaflet. I was hoping to get to interview him.
那超出了我的职权范围
Well, that's above my pay grade.
我只是受命来告诉你我们的工作
I was just asked to show you what we do
还有回答一些问题
and answer some questions.
这是你们要做的事吗
And this is what you do?
我们巡逻街道  保证人类免受外星人的伤害
We patrol the streets, keep them safe for humans,
就像你当守护者那样
just like you do with Guardian.
这个星期很特别
This week is special.
我们不想任何蟑螂毁掉大家的感恩节晚宴
We don't want any roaches crashing people's Thanksgiving dinners.
蟑螂
"Roaches"?
这个词太严重了  如果你不在我面前
That's pretty heavy language, and I would really appreciate it
把外星人叫做蟑螂  我会很感激你
if you didn't call aliens "Roaches" in my presence.
但他们就是
But that's what they are.
还是说你把他们这样分类
Or do you just classify them that way
就不用去面对  他们事实上
so you don't have to deal with the fact
和你我一样是活生生  有呼吸的生命
that they're living, breathing beings just like you and I?
真好笑  因为我看过你
That's funny 'cause I've seen you
你作为守护者  不也经常消灭他们吗
decimate quite a few of them yourself as Guardian.
但我也会与违反法律的人类斗争
And I also fight against humans that break the law.
-又是你妻子吗  -对  我得给她打个电话
- Your wife again? - Yeah, I better give her a call.
你能帮我牵一下狗吗
Do you mind holding onto that?
谢谢
Thanks.
"自由之子"
"Children of Liberty."
这名字可真够蠢的
Well, that's a stupid name, innit?
戴面具做什么  懦弱到不敢露脸吗
What's with the mask? Too cowardly to show your face, eh?
诡异的镜片
Weird lenses.
好了  我再问你一次
Right, I'm gonna ask you once more.
自由代表是谁  我去哪里可以找到他
Who is Agent Liberty and where can I find him?
别再逼我对你用这些玩意了
Don't give me a reason to have to use these.
求你了  我已经说了
Please, it's like I said.
我刚拿到面具
I just got the mask.
他们就让我在街上巡逻  吓吓蟑螂
I'm supposed to patrol the street and scare roaches.
我只知道这些
That is all I know.
我想让你少受点折磨
Well, I tried to save you some suffering.
看来有些人就是喜欢受虐
It seems like some blokes are just masochists.
我要是能透过你这颗大脑袋
If only I could see into this big,
看穿你的想法就好了
ugly head of yours.
话又说回来
Actually...
也许我可以
Maybe I can.
卡拉·丹弗斯家  感恩晚宴  霍普街16号
大多数外星人就像人类一样渴望平静生活
Most aliens want to live peacefully just like humans do.
是吗  证据在哪里
Okay, and where's the proof in that?
现在已经出现过多起外星人袭击案件
Because there have been numerous alien attacks,
许多人类丢了性命
human lives have been lost.
但是也不乏外星人做出杰出贡献的例子
But there are also aliens making extraordinary contributions.
拍摄《纳欣诺市外星人》系列片时
Every one that I interviewed for
我采访的每位外星人都非常优秀
my Aliens in National City series was exceptional.
好  不过我们现在
Okay, but for a second,
可以先关注一下人类例外论
let's just talk about human exceptionalism.
比如你们的主编  詹姆斯·奥尔森
For example, your own editor in chief, James Olsen.
今晚来上节目的本应是他  对不对
He was supposed to be here tonight, was he not?
-是的  -好的  守护者
- Uh, yes. - Okay, so Guardian,
如果自由之子确实成了问题
if the Children of Liberty are such a problem,
守护者为什么没有宣布与他们决裂
why hasn't Guardian renounced them?
事实上  我听说他正在与他们会面
In fact, rumor is he's meeting with them right now,
这就意味着  詹姆斯·奥尔森认为
which seems to indicate that James Olsen understands
这些人的言论有一定价值
that these people have something of value to say.
言论有价值是一码事  但传播仇恨言论
There is a very clear difference between having something to say
完全是另一码事
and the hate speech in these leaflets.
这种宣言只会造成暴力和恐慌
This manifesto will only incite violence and fear,
作为美国人  我们不应该做这种事
and as Americans, we are better than that.
尤其是在感恩节  明天就是感恩节
On Thanksgiving, tomorrow is Thanksgiving.
这是家庭的节日  也是社区的节日
It is a day for family, for our community.
这一天  我们尊重文化  求同存异
It is about welcoming different cultures
共同表达对生命的诚挚谢意
and celebrating a gratitude for life together.
这才是自由的真正意义
That is what liberty is about.
也许我们的对话应该到此为止...
Maybe that's a good place to end this conver--
你说得非常好
That's a really good point.
抱歉  我需要回应一下这番话
I'm sorry, I just need to respond to that.
我觉得我们今天在这里
I think it's very interesting
在感恩节的前一天
that we are here, having this debate
讨论这个话题非常有趣
the day before Thanksgiving Day.
在美国的历史上存在一个恶习
I mean, American history,
人们总是在这个特定的节日里
it has this nasty habit with this holiday particularly
把一切包裹起来  粉饰太平
to just wrap it all up in a neat little bow,
但事实是
when the truth is in the
多年前  万帕诺亚格土著居民
years following the indigenous Wampanoag people
邀请朝圣者享用美好的感恩宴
inviting the pilgrims to a wonderful Thanksgiving meal,
可是欧洲入侵者却屠杀了那些东道主
the European invaders slaughtered their hosts.
如果我们不从美国历史上吸取教训
So if we do not learn from American history.
那么很有可能
Is it possible
一百年后
that 100 years from now, the
外星人将拥有他们自己的感恩节
aliens will have their own wonderful, thankful holiday
庆祝他们对我们的屠杀
about how they slaughtered us?
-我...  -对  说得好
- I--  - Yeah! That's right.
你没想过用真的蔓越莓吗
You didn't think about using real cranberries?
那也不会比这个强多少
Well, like that's any better than this.
这个看起来确实好消化一些
Well, it does look easier to digest.
听到观众为洛克伍德的话欢呼
I'm still feeling queasy from hearing
我还是有点犯恶心
the audience cheer for Lockwood.
不必太自责
Look, don't beat yourself up, okay?
本来甚至都不应该是你去上节目
Yeah, that wasn't even supposed to be you up there.
我去开门
I can get it.
这不是我的跟踪狂吗
Oh. Well, if it isn't my stalker.
尼娅·纳尔  我没想到你也会来
Nia Nal. I didn't realize you were going to be here.
所以这些花不是送给我的吗
So those flowers aren't for me?
不是  是送卡拉的
Uh, no, they're for Kara.
之前有人跟我说  永远不要空手拜访
I was once told to always show up not empty-handed.
看来你妈妈把你教得很好
Sounds like your mother raised you right.
其实她并没有
No, she most definitely did not.
布莱尼  你能来太好了
Brainy, I'm so glad you made it.
这些花好漂亮
These are lovely.
不是真花
They're not real.
荣恩在吗
Hi. Is J'onn here?
-在  -我是曼彻斯特
- Yeah. - I'm Manchester.
你好  我是卡拉  幸会
Oh, hi. I'm Kara, it's very nice to meet you.
我对你的事迹早有耳闻
I've heard so much about you.
我对你的遭遇表示遗憾
I am sorry for your loss.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你
Thanks.
-你来了  -对  忽然饿了
- You made it. - Yeah, got hungry.
这个问题很好解决
Oh, we can take care of that.
我是伊莉莎  卡拉和艾丽克斯的妈妈
I am Eliza, Kara and Alex's mom.
你是艾丽克斯的妈妈吗
You're Alex's mum?
她挺难管的吧
Yeah, she's quite a inch, isn't she?
多谢夸奖
Thank you?
我来帮你
Oh, let me give you a hand.
谢了  尼娅
Thanks, Nia.
那天我见到超女了
Saw Supergirl the other night.
对  她提到了  说你帮了大忙
Yeah, she mentioned that. Said you were quite helpful.
希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind,
但卡拉跟我说了你有嗜睡症
but Kara told me about your narcolepsy.
其实没什么大不了的
Oh, it's really not that big of a deal.
我朋友  莫杰医生很擅长治疗睡眠失调问题
My friend, Dr. Moger is a specialist in sleep disorders
她就在纳欣诺市
right here in National City.
天哪  这也太巧了
Oh, my gosh, what an unexpected coincidence.
我已经给她发了短信  下周随时可以为你看病
I've already texted her, she can get you in any time next week.
不  不用了  谢谢你
No! No, thank you, um...
我已经找到医生了
I already have a doctor here.
是哪一位呢  也许我认识
Oh. Who? Maybe I know them?
是史密斯医生
Uh, Dr. Smith.
是吉恩·史密斯吗
Gene Smith?
不是  是明斯基
No, um... Uh, Minsky?
明斯基·史密斯医生
Dr. Minsky Smith.
他很年轻  您肯定不认识他
He's really young, I'm sure you don't know him.
我的意思不是您不认识年轻人
Not that you don't know young people.
没关系
It's okay.
我去拿点纸巾
I'm gonna go get some napkins.
你永远不会用超能力对付别人吗
So you would never use your powers against someone?
哪怕是阻止暴力行为
Not even to stop more violence?
为了自保可能会
Well, in defense I might.
那读心术呢
What about mind reading?
这不算暴力
That's not violence.
如果未经别人同意就是一种暴力
It's a type of violence if done without consent.
偷窥别人的私密想法
Prying in to someone's personal thoughts.
为什么这么问
Why do you ask?
我在想小菲
Just thinking about Fi.
如果她看到情况恶化至此
I'm wondering what she would do if she were here to see
不知会怎么做
how bad things are getting.
你来了
You made it.
当然
Um, of course.
我还以为你要跟你的新朋友一起吃饭呢
I just thought you'd be sitting down to dinner with your new friends.
-你收到我的短信了吗  -收到了
- Did you get my message? - Yeah.
你还是去见了他们吗
Did you still go meet with them?
对
Yeah.
那好吧
Well, there you go.
你跟自由之子的联络怎么样了
How did things go with your Children of Liberty contact?
那不太安全吧  詹姆斯
Doesn't seem very safe, James.
我恰好碰见一个叫汤姆的普通人
I happened to meet with a regular guy named Tom
他害怕外星人
who happens to be afraid of aliens,
害怕他们的超能力
and afraid of their capabilities,
害怕低人一等
and he feels inferior.
人类也可以有很强的能力
People can be powerful, too.
你和艾丽克斯就是例子  詹姆斯
You and Alex are examples of that, James.
但却不如外星人强
Yeah, but not as powerful as aliens.
你再怎么练举重
I mean, no matter how many weights
都不可能像超女一样有力
you lift you'll never be as strong as Supergirl.
是不可能  但在科技的帮助下
No, but with technology
我们也可以当英雄
we can hold our own.
要是我们能更进一步呢
What if we could do more?
要是我们能让人类也有超能力呢
What if we could make people super?
不可能
It's not possible.
让外星人拥有超能力的生化过程
The biological processes that cause alien powers
跟人类DNA不相容
are incompatible with human DNA.
行  那假如我们可以  行吧
Okay, but just say we could, right?
如果詹姆斯说得对
If James is right
那些人是因为害怕低人一等
and people feeling inferior
才加入仇恨组织
is what makes them join these hate groups,
那我们就让他们公平竞争
then we could just level the playing field.
我们可不想看到
The last thing we need is a bunch of evil people
一帮有超能力的恶人到处乱窜
running around with super powers.
但恶人得不到超能力
Okay, but evil people wouldn't get powers.
所以只有某些人有资格
So only certain people qualify?
那谁来决定哪些人有资格呢
And who would decide who gets them?
这些人就要扮演上帝了
They'd be playing God.
开吃吧
Let's eat!
我在《今日辩论》上看到你了
Hey, I saw you on Counterpoint Daily.
抱歉让你临时顶替我
I'm really sorry to put you out there like that last minute.
我只是担心这个宣言
I just worry that this manifesto
预示着会有坏事发生
really is a harbinger of something terrible.
我们在文本里发现很多隐藏信息
In the text, we found numerous hidden messages,
但最具威胁性的也只是与熟食店相关而已
but even the most threatening was about charcuterie.
更可怕的是
It seems scarier now that
他们已经训练出能判别外星人的狗了
they've trained dogs to identify aliens.
-真的吗  -真的
- They have? - Yup.
前几天晚上跟超女对打的那个人就有条狗
Actually, the guy Supergirl fought the other night had a dog.
你在想什么  詹姆斯
What are you thinking, James?
我和汤姆昨天去遛狗的时候
Tom and I were walking his dog yesterday
它朝着几户人家不停地叫
and the dog kept barking at certain houses.
外星人家
Alien houses.
他们做了什么标记吗
Did they mark them somehow?
他一直在给别人发短信  他说是他妻子
He kept texting somebody, who he claimed to be his wife.
但我猜他可能是发短信给别人
But I guess he could have been texting somebody else
好标记出那些地址  便于以后行动
to mark those addresses for later.
他们标记出外星人的房子
The only reason they'd
只有一个原因  那就是把他们当做攻击目标
wanna identify alien homes is to target them.
对  但如果他们给房子做了标记
Yeah, but if they were marking houses
我们应该能看到或注意到吧
we would see that, right? We would notice that.
标记可能是肉眼看不见的
The marks might not be visible to the naked eye.
面具上有夜视技术
The mask had some kind of night vision tech in them.
你吃饭怎么还把那东西带来了
Why did you bring that to dinner?
我想着要是无聊了
Oh, uh, I figured if things got boring
就做点工作
I might just do a little work.
你们看
Oh, look at that.
这是个低频谱增强器
Wait, that's a low spectrum enhancer.
用这个可以看到红外线
You use it to see infrared.
给我看看
Here, let me see that.
那边  我看到一个
Look at that, I see one there.
所以他们准备发动袭击
Right, so they're gonna attack.
问题是什么时候
The question is, when?
"美国最后的暮光"
"Twilight's last gleaming."
这是他们宣言的标题
It's the title of their manifesto.
说明了袭击的时间
Tells them when to strike.
最后的暮光就是日落
Twilight's last gleaming is sunset.
那我们没多少时间了
Then we don't have much time.
派对很愉快  感恩
Great party, Thanksgiving.
听着
Um, here, look.
还有二十分钟日落
Sunset is in 20 minutes.
我要去工作  你能载我一程吗
I gotta get to work so can you give me a ride?
哈雷不会支援我们  但我会尽可能解决街头问题
Haley won't back us up but I'll do what I can at street level.
我尽可能地清除标记
I'll get rid of as many markers as I can
这样他们就不知道该袭击哪里
so they won't know where to attack.
我也要走了
I'm gonna go, too.
我和汤姆沟通过  也许我能开导他
I connected with Tom. Maybe I can talk some sense into them.
要是他们不听呢
And if they don't listen?
那我就想办法让他们听
Then I will find a way to make them listen.
这算什么计划
That's not a plan.
我现在没空说这个了
I don't have time to talk about this right now.
他们也没空说这个
They don't have time to talk,
他们就是来挑起战争的
either. They're out there looking for a fight.
我很感谢你努力帮我  真的
I appreciate the fact that you're trying to help me, I do,
但我不需要你的帮助  我自己能行
but I don't need it. I'm gonna be fine.
因为你能解决吗
Right, because you can handle it?
对  我自己能解决
Yes, I can handle myself.
我不需要你为了
I don't need you freaking out
我生活里的每一点小麻烦操心
about every little problem that I have in my life.
就地方检察官的事来说吧
Now, take the DA for example.
你这么紧张那件事
You got all worked up about that
结果也没出什么问题
and it turned out to be fine.
好吗  我要走了
Okay? I'm going.
没出问题是因为被我解决了
It was fine because I made it fine.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
我和地方检察官谈过话了  詹姆斯
I talked to the DA, James.
我拿布鲁诺·曼海姆的信息跟她交换
I traded information about Bruno Mannheim,
她就撤销了指控
she dropped the indictment.
什么
You did what?
你听到了
You heard me.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
再给我一次机会  我还是会这么干
I would do it again in a heartbeat.
我爱你  只要能护你安全
I love you, and there is no line in the universe
我愿意做任何过分的事
I would not cross to keep you safe.
如果你把这当成是爱
If that's what you think love is,
那我大概不想要这种爱
I'm not sure if I want any part of that.
今年轮到我来做祷告了
Well, I guess this year it's my job to say grace.
我要感谢我的家人
I am thankful for my family.
你们相信我  支持我
You have believed in me, you've supported me.
尽管我知道这很不容易
Even though I know it's been a struggle.
我目睹了你们的能力
I see your power,
你们的力量
I see your strength,
这一年里我们经历了
and there has been so very much this year
太多的斗争
to fight against.
但今天  你们让我感到我们能再次取胜
But today, you make me feel like we can win again.
只要我们齐心协力  就能崛起  就能取胜
Together we will rise and we will overcome.
别这么做
Do not do this.
这是每个人都必须做的决定
These are choices everyone has to make.
我的家人最重要
It is my family first!
别让你的怒火变成暴力
Do not let your anger become violence.
有些底线是不能跨越的
There are lines that we do not cross.
给我让开
Get out of my way!
我只想保护我的家人
I just wanna protect my family.
你也会这么做的
You'd do the same thing.
我不会选择这种方式
Not like this, I wouldn't.
我觉得我没法找到所有标记
I don't think I can find them all.
别害怕  我也在街上抹除标记
Never fear. I'm also on the streets removing markers.
事实上  我现在就看到了一个
In fact, I see one right now.
你在干什么
Hey, what are you doing?
回家去吧
Return to your homes.
-要不然  -要不然怎样
- Or else. - Or else what?
要不然我就会揍你们一顿
Or else I'll be required to beat you up.
用物理学
With physics.
那里有一个
There's one!
出来  你们这些肮脏的蟑螂
Get out here, you filthy roaches!
对不起  小菲
Sorry, Fi.
我得按我的方式去做
I've got to do it my way.
出来  出来  不管你在哪里
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
往后靠
Stay back.
躲不了咯  蟑螂
Can't hide, roach.
这是我们的家  我在这住了很多年
This is our home! We've lived here for years.
你不能再藏在形象诱发器后面了
You can't hide behind that image inducer any longer.
尖刺  想想办法  拜托
Spike, do something. Please!
艾丽克斯  主街上有一条龙
Alex, there's a dragon on Main Street.
我引用《哈利波特》就是这种下场
That's what I get for making a Harry Potter reference.
我觉得他不喜欢这样
I don't think he likes that.
不  别伤害他
No! Don't hurt him!
他只是想要保护我们
He's just trying to protect us.
超女  我和一个小女孩在一起  她叫阿兰娜
Supergirl, hey, I'm here with a little girl, her name is Alana.
这条龙是她的宠物  名字叫尖刺
So the dragon is her pet, his name is Spike.
他的行为只是在防卫
And he's just acting defensively,
他在试图保护她的家人
he's trying to protect her family.
尖刺  尖刺...
Spike! Spike...
尖刺  阿兰娜安全了
Spike! Alana's safe.
你做得好  你保护了她
You did your job. You protected her.
你很忠诚  你很真实
You were loyal, you were true.
你保证了每个人的安全
You kept everyone safe.
好孩子
Good boy.
虽然狗不再喜欢我了
Well, dogs may not like me anymore,
但龙还是喜欢我的
but I still got it with dragons.
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers.
再说一次  你和超女违背了我的直接命令
Once again, you and Supergirl have disobeyed my direct orders.
我告诉过你这个宣言并不是当务之急
I told you this manifesto was not a matter of priority.
哈雷上校  你必须...
Colonel Haley, you have to--
即便如此
That said,
自由之子的暴力行为刺激了
the violent actions of the Children of Liberty are stirring
纳欣诺市最危险的外星人进行自卫
National City's most dangerous aliens to defend themselves.
我们不能再继续激怒他们了
And we must make sure not to provoke them any further.
所以  从现在开始
So, from this point forward
我们会考虑把自由之子
we will consider the Children of Liberty
当做超查部的首要任务
a matter of priority for the DEO.
谢谢你  哈雷上校
Thank you, Colonel Haley.
你们可以走了
You are dismissed.
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers.
别以为我不知道我眼皮底下
Don't think there is anything that happens under my watch
都发生了什么
that I'm not aware of.
我随时都可以阻止你未经批准的调查
I could've stopped your little rogue investigation at any moment.
但是我却任由你自取灭亡
But I gave you just enough rope to hang yourself.
对你来说幸运的是
Fortunately for you,
这一次你有了我的批准
this time you had a chair to stand on.
但你再也不许违背我的直接命令了
But do not ever disobey my direct orders again
不然后果会不堪设想
or there will be consequences.
我遵循了自己的直觉  事情证明我是对的
I followed my instincts and they were right.
我还会继续这么做
And I will continue to do so
因为这正是我作为一名出色领袖的特质
because that is what makes me a great leader.
如果这意味着你要以军法审判我
And if that means that you have to court-martial me,
那就这样吧
then so be it.
再说一次  钢铁女侠再次施展了自己的本领
Once again, the Girl of Steel proving just what she's made of.
宝贝
Honey.
宝贝  有你的电话
Honey, you have a call.
是节目上那个女人打来的
It's the woman from the show.
肖恩  你好吗
Hey, Sean, how are you doing?
好的
Okay.
太不可思议了
Well, that's incredible.
我自己的节目
My own show.
不  当然  我当然愿意
Uh, no, of course. Of course!
我很乐意做这件事
I would love to do it.
伊莉莎这么快就走了  她通常会多留几天
Eliza left so soon. She usually stays a few days.
她要去参加...  看我能不能说对
She had to get to her, let me see if I get this right,
...族群异种生物学会议
ethno-xeno biology conference
她将在会上谈论
where she is speaking about
陆生儿童的退化遗传特征
the regressive hereditary traits of inter-terrestrial children.
我真的很高兴她没有跟尼娅讲这些
Wow, I'm really glad she didn't talk to Nia about that
因为她会把尼娅说睡的
'cause she would have put her right to sleep.
我之前看到她们两个在说话
I did see the two of them talking, though.
妈妈想给她找个医生
Mom was trying to find her a doctor,
但是尼娅说她已经有了
but Nia said she already had one.
真奇怪  她告诉我说她还没有找到
That's weird. She told me she hadn't found one yet.
为什么她要说谎呢
Why would she lie about that?
抱歉你在为朋友担心
I'm sorry you're worried about your friend,
但是至少你让哈雷特工把自由之子
but at least you got Agent Haley to make the Children of Liberty
当成了超查部的当务之急  这是件好事
an urgent matter for the DEO. That's a big win.
我们确实阻止了
Well, we did stop the
自由之子伤害无辜的外星人
Children of Liberty from hurting innocent aliens.
但是自由代表还在逃
But Agent Liberty is still out there.
仇恨言论也在滋长
And the rhetoric of hate is growing.
只是还没弄清楚怎么赢得这场战斗
Just haven't figured out how to win this fight yet.
有这么多人心怀恐惧地站出来支持
With so many people siding with fear,
这件事会发展到什么程度
how far will this go?
历史告诉我们  这种事件会一发不可收拾
History tells us moments like this can get very, very ugly.
我曾经亲眼见过
I've seen it with my own eyes.
我们这次赢了
We won this time.
但是这场战斗很特殊
But this is gonna be a fight like no other.
往前进一步就会后退两步
It's gonna be one step forward and two steps back.
詹姆斯
James.
谢谢你来见我
Thanks for meeting me.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
我昨晚应该见的那些人
All those guys I was supposed to meet last night,
他们都不见了
they all went missing.
汤姆  如果我们不及时阻止事态发展
Tom, the violence is only gonna get worse
暴力只会越发严重
if we don't stop this now.
听着
Look,
我没法直接接触到自由代表
I don't have direct access to Agent Liberty.
不过我可以帮你牵线
But I can connect you with people who do.
但是我要警告你
But I... I gotta warn you,
这些人很危险
these guys are dangerous.
我总得试试  伙计
I gotta try, man.
你要接电话吗
You need to take that?
莉娜来电
不用
No.
我什么时候能见那些人
When can I meet these guys?
现在
Now.
卢瑟女士  你还好吗
Ms. Luthor? Are you all right?
外面越来越危险了
It's getting more dangerous out there.
感觉我们与外星人的内战就快打响了
Feels like we're on the verge of a civil war with the aliens.
我们所爱的人会需要我们保护
The people we love are gonna need our protection.
我想推进哈伦·艾尔协议
I want to move forward with the Harun-El protocol.
我们需要进行人体试验
We're gonna need a human subject.
是考德威尔
It's Caldwell.
好了  我就知道这些  我听从考德威尔的命令
Okay, that's all I know. I take my orders from Caldwell.
太奇怪了
That's so odd.
不不不  不不不不
No, no, no. No, no, no, no.
求你了  求你了  你没必要这么做
Please, please, you don't have to do this.